Makazaki.
Here.
If I were you, I'd take a seat.
Yes, sir.
Sora?
It's been a while, Taka.
This is the first time we've really seen each other in ten long years.
Which included France and the Holy Roman Empire.
I remember that day he first transferred here.
It was right around our seasonal uniform change.
Hello.
I'm, uh, the transfer student.
Okay, great.
My name is Kodaka.
Nice to be here.
Oh no, Ms. Osada.
Did he just attack her?
Deliquent much?
He's new here.
What's up with his hair?
Taka.
It's Taka.
I'd recognize that hair and expression anywhere.
It's definitely him.
He hasn't changed a bit in the last ten years.
He always did suck at smiling.
And the harder he tried to be nice and friendly to people, the more it would just backfire on him.
I can't believe it.
Oh, I forgot my book.
Here, take mine.
Oh, thanks.
Yeah, that's him.
It's Taka.
My one and only friend when I was a kid.
He didn't even notice me.
Well, tell me what you think, Tomo.
Yeah.
Taka.
Or Kodaka Hasegawa.
My best friend from back when I was a kid who doesn't even remember who I am now.
Isn't that the worst?
Yeah.
My best guess is that it's because I used to dress like a boy whenever we hung out together.
And yeah, I get that, but still.
No way!
Why should I have to be the one to talk to him?
I mean, think about it.
I have no idea how to start a conversation with somebody.
I don't know.
I thought maybe I could get him to talk to me first.
When I get to school, when I leave the class after school, when I put things in my locker,
or take them back out, I always have to walk by him.
But he never says a single word to me.
It's not like that at all.
What do you mean it's my fault?
Right.
Yeah.
And you know what, Tomo?
You make a really good point.
Do you want to go shopping after school?
I need some eyeliner.
Sure.
Let's try that makeup place across from the station.
I think I do remember that.
No, I can't believe this!
Crap!
Kodaka saw me.
Could he hear me talking?
I'm gonna die.
Please don't tell me you heard what I was saying.
This is bad.
This is really bad.
What do I do?
What do you want?
I was just wondering, do you like to see ghosts and stuff?
What?
Uh, no, because ghosts don't exist.
Well then, who have you been talking to?
You were watching me?
Look, I was having a conversation with my best friend ever.
She's made her air, okay?
And that was the first conversation I had had with Taka in ten years.
Also, I'm an idiot.
That's perfect.
A club!
Huh?
See you later, Kodaka.
That's it.
I'll start a club.
Here's a new club application for you.
Thank you so much, sir.
If I'm not in a club, I can make one.
A club just for me and Kodaka.
Sometimes I use this chapel when I need a quiet place to read, or when the library's too crowded
for me to focus.
It's always really comforting.
Sister Maria Takeyama is supposed to be in charge of this room.
Apparently, she's still a child.
I guess it's good I don't hate kids.
Excuse me.
Hey, you!
Why the hell are you in here?
This is my holy room for napping, so get out!
It's not a place for scummy sinners like you!
Um, hi, my name is Yosara Mikazuki, and I'm from Class 2-5.
If you're Sister Maria, I'm supposed to ask you...
Forget it!
What a little brat!
Okay, I think if you just heard me out, you'd say that...
I don't listen to poopy heads!
Oh, you're gonna listen.
I'm applying to start a new after-school club, and I was hoping I could use this room.
No means no!
Now get out of here, you grody plop of poop!
It's time.
Kodaka, follow me, please.
Holy crap, she talked to him.
To that Hasekawa creep?
Now, let the clubbing begin.
Our purpose can be to help us make friends.
Perfect.
A club for me and Kodaka.
Taka and Sora.
This way, we'll be able to become friends again like we used to be.
Now, let's see.
How often should we open your patience?
Oh
Hey, Asagawa
Why is he staring at Yuzuru like that?
They're still standing
Hello
All right, moving on with attendance
Miyajimi
Here
Butto
Yagashi
Sorry, yeah, I'm here
Good
Yamazaki
Here
That's when I said
So, um, hey
Hey, what?
I was just, what happened to your hair?
Got it cut?
Yeah, well, I can kind of see that
But, like, why did you cut it?
Blame that summer festival night
But that was just the tip, right?
It's not like the whole thing got destroyed
You didn't have to cut off so much
I did have to cut this mud off
Because you totally soaked my head
No matter how many times I washed my hair
That freaking stench would not come out
Oh, I'm really sorry
Please, I, uh
Soaked her head?
He said just the tip, but did he force her?
Yeah, that is not cool
She washed and washed
But couldn't get the gross stink of his stuff out of her hair
You're wrong
I was only doing what had to be done
Shut up and come on
Wait, what?
Yozora
Okay
I, uh
What I'm trying to say is
You're right, okay?
I was Sora
So what are you thinking?
I'm, uh
Pretty surprised
And anything else?
Like what?
You know, like else
Like, are you happy?
Maybe honored?
Or are you moved at all?
Hmm, how do I put it?
I'm bewildered by the whole thing
Surprised
Yeah, that's definitely the strongest feeling right now
Oh
That haircut does look really good on you
Uh, uh, um
Thanks
You don't think it's weird?
No
It's nice
Oh
Thank you
I actually went to a hair salon
Wow
That must have been fun
Was it what you expected?
I was nervous
Yeah, I can imagine that you were
Hold on a sec
You knew who I was the day I transferred here?
Yep
I knew from the very beginning
And I'm surprised yet again
Don't be
I'd recognize your pudding head anywhere
Thank you
Well, you certainly could have fooled me
Wait
But don't you remember that day when we met in the classroom?
I swear you said something about not remembering what my name was
Hmm
I was pretty irritated that I recognized who you were
Even though you didn't have a clue about me
So you pretended you didn't know me instead?
That's right
Crap, we're at a dead end
I'm sorry if I seemed rude
But, I mean, how can you blame me for that?
It's not like I'd ever seen you wearing a skirt, right?
You were only ever dressed like a boy
Who cares what I wore?
I never once told you I was a boy when we were kids
Sorry, it's just you don't normally see girls wearing boys' clothes
And picking fights with other boys whenever they could
I was going to tell you I was a girl
But you up and disappeared before I got the chance to
Are you serious?
That was the important thing you said you were going to tell me?
But you never showed up that day
And I waited
A long time
You're wrong
Because I did show up then
But I got too embarrassed
I was in a skirt
And
And I was afraid you would laugh at me
You what?
I wore a skirt because I wanted to confess to you I was a girl
I figured that was the best way to let you know
But I'd never worn a skirt before
So I didn't know if it looked good on me or not
I thought maybe you would laugh at me
I just
I couldn't make myself do it
It was way too embarrassing
But if I'd known you were moving
I might have gotten up the courage to actually go for it
You see?
This whole thing is all your fault
There's no way
Because first of all, weirdo
You didn't have to wear a skirt to tell me
Whatever
You know for a fact
If I had just told you
You never would have believed me
Yeah
You're probably right
I think
Well
The fact we were friends
I mean
I think the fact we were acquaintances
Should remain a secret from the rest of the club
How come?
There's no reason for them to know
Uh
Sure
That's fine
Good
Then that's that
Okay, let's go
One sec
Hmm?
I don't know what to call you now
What do you want me to use?
Yozura
You can use my first name
Don't you have a nickname or something easier for me to say?
I do
Did?
Look, I'm not going to tell you what it was, Kodaka
Why not?
Because only
Only real friends use nicknames with each other
Hey guys
Oh hello, Kodaka
What's going on?
A double dose of hotness with Kodaka and a mystery stud muffin
Huh?
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god
Tell Rika who this hot boy is
Tell her, tell her, tell her
Tell you who this hot boy is?
Do you not see this shirt?
No, wait
Before you tell her who this hot boy delight is
Rika will try to deduce the answer
Here she goes
He must be your first younger friend
Wrong
So then your first older friend?
No
Is he your younger brother?
Don't have one
Then he's your older brother
I don't have any brothers
Huh
We must be looking at your soccer rival
I have not, nor will I ever play soccer
Is he the president of your student body?
I don't know what that means
Then tell me he's your fiance
How do you come up with these?
Alas, my big bro Kodaka has left me for a stud muffin
What the hell are you talking about, Yukimura?
This is hot
Rika wonders which one's the dominant
Which one's the submissive
Does Kodaka like to be the aggressive dom?
Or is he masochistically submissive?
Reluctant dom or reluctant sub?
Rika bets it's hardcore to matter what they do
Oh, just imagining it makes Rika
She's such a freak job
Get it together
This is just
Hey
Huh?
Yozara
You got your hair cut
Well, yeah
Thank you, Captain Obvious
Oh
Yozara
What's up?
Who?
Uh
Yozara
It's you
That's right
I am still me
You chopped a ton of your hair off, lady
So
What'd you do it for?
It doesn't have anything to do with you, meek
Oh, come on
Why not just tell me?
It won't cost you anything
Nothing except for my precious time
What?
Are you saying that talking to me is a waste of time?
You said it, sister
And things are back to normal
You!
Stay right here until Rika gets back!
What's she up to now?
Hmm?
Now then
Did you cut it because of a broken heart?
Shut up
Yes!
That's it, right?
You totally just lost a lover
Awesome!
I said shut up
Poor mean old Yozara had love ripped away from her
I wonder why
So spill it
Who is this lucky fella anyway?
Whoever it is deserves a medal for realizing what a massive tool you are in kicking you to the curb
How could you hit my face?
That's sacred!
I do not have a broken heart, you idiot
However, now I know how you would react if I did get my heart broken
Which helps to prove how awful you truly are
Well, that sucks
I thought I'd finally get the chance to bully her, but I guess not
If your heart hasn't been stomped on, then why did you cut it?
You don't get to know that
Oh, come on!
Tell me!
Okay, Yozara
Will you please try this on?
What is that?
Is it like a dance uniform from somewhere?
You're exactly right, yeah!
This is an original, legitimate white uniform coat
Officially worn by the student council president
Of the one and only Galford Academy!
Of Galford Academy?
Yes, and for real, Yozara
Rika knows this is going to look amazing on you
But isn't this just like a cosplay uniform thing?
Why would I want to dress up in a costume in the middle of the day?
Because it'll look amazing!
Rika already said so!
Hey, big brother!
It's so good to see you!
Wow, someone's sure in a good mood today
Huh?
Why are you standing out in the hallway?
Oh, you were caught being naughty again, weren't you?
Uh, just what do you mean by again?
Okay, guys, come in
What did Rika say?
Amazing, right?
Yeah, she looks...
There's a hot guy!
There's a really hot guy in here!
Why are you so scared, Maria?
Because everyone knows hot guys chew up and spit out cute little girls like me!
That's what all the other sisters say
And I don't want to be gnawed on just because I'm this adorable!
Hey, cutie, I'm gonna munch on you
I don't taste good at all, so please leave me alone!
Go away!
I'm going to munch you, okay?
And then I'm going to crunch
Didn't we go through this exact same thing already?
Kodaka, about my summer homework, I...
Huh?
Take her!
If you're gonna eat anybody, it should be a vampire!
She'll taste better than me, I swear it!
You're gonna eat me?
No.
Um, no one's eating you
I will!
I'll hit Kobito into little pieces
Let me have at her!
Hey, what was that for?
You should be ashamed of yourself, meatwad
You have serious issues
Oh, great
She shows up after disappearing for a week
And even though she has a whole new look
Yozara's still just Yozara
You better believe it
Why would I ever want to change?
I'm perfect the way I am
I don't know what to call you now
What do you want me to use?
Sora?
I'm perfect
Call me by my name
Yozara
Like you've been doing
That sound good?
Kodaka?
Sounds good
Yozara
Great
Yozara and I
Well
No, I guess Sora and Taka used to be best friends
But now
Yozara, Mikazuki, and Kodaka Hasegawa aren't
I know that Yozara was Sora
But we can't just pick up where we left off ten years ago, can we?
Can we?
I wonder
What will happen to us after this?
Okay, at least tell me why it's so short
I don't have to tell you why I do what I do to my hair
I don't really know the answer
You're so rude
I hope so
So you know how slanty your eyes are
Your eyes are slanted too
I think though
That's why I should stick around here for a while
Oh!
You're a poopy vampire!
What do you know?
Or a disciple of God
Here in this club
Where all we're trying to do is make some friends
Are cool
Or you are crazy
Oh!
Now, it's time to begin theigi They were club activities for the New term
So asso, I won't remember
follow me
Tou cat, getMargG Lenray
Karen's Herrett
Don't you even want to
We're multitasking,arenver
No be scared to
So funny
I don't know
Angen
We play
Hey, why is there a preview on the last episode?
Mm-hmm. You let your guard down too easily.
We're having an extra episode.
Why? So what's it gonna be about?
That's a secret.
Tell me.
Okie dokie.
So it's not a secret.
It's legendary.
An episode banned from television
and never before revealed to anyone.
I didn't realize we had one of those.
And the epic title is...
A Round Robin Story's Ending is Way Extreme.
Here she goes.
The Round Robin Story, The Door to a Forbidden World.
CEREMO
Rightirs by The белый
Thunder
Academy
Benny
Man
The
Re
We